Guide to the Hannah Green Letters to Vincent McHugh, 1957-1959
Department of Special Collections
Hannah Green Letters to Vincent McHugh,
1957-1959
Special Collections M1004
Green, Hannah.
1.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchased, 1998.
Biography
American writer. Received her masters' degree under Wallace Stegner at Stanford University, 1956. Known particularly for her THE DEAD OF THE HOUSE, 1972.
Access Terms
McHugh, Vincent, 1904-; American literature--20th century.
Container List
- Original Accession
  - 1957, August (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/22/57
    - TLS, 2pp. 8/28/57
    - TLS, 4pp. 8/31/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/31/57
  - 1957, September (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - TLS/ALS, 4pp. 9/9/57
    - TLS, 1p. 9/10/57
    - ALS, 1p. 9/11/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/19/57
    - ALS, 1p. 9/24/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/26/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/27/57
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/29/57
    - TLS, 3pp. Cozzens' By Love Possessed. 9/30/57
  - 1957, October 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - TLS, 1p. 10/2/57
    - TLS, 4pp. 10/2/57
    - TLS, 1p. 10/3/57
    - TLS/ALS, 4pp. 10/4/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/7/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/8/57
    - ALS, 1p. 10/9/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/9/57
    - TLS, 4pp. 10/12/57
    - TLS, 3pp. 10/14/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/14/57
    - ALS, 1p. 10/15/57
  - 1957, October 16-31 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - TLS, 2pp. 10/16/57
    - TLS, 2pp. 10/18/57
    - ALS, 1p. 10/19/57
    - TLS, 3pp. 10/22/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/23/57
    - TLS, 2pp. 10/23/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/25/57
    - TLS, 4pp. Camus' The Fall. Includes a check for $50.00 10/26/57
  - ALS, 2pp. 10/28/57 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/28/57
    - TLS, 2pp. 10/30/57
  - 1957, November (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/1/57
    - ALS, 1p. 11/1/57
    - TLS, 2pp. 11/2/57
    - TLS, 2pp. 11/4/57
    - ALS, 1p. 11/4/57
    - TLS, 2pp. 11/5/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/5/57
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/8/57
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/8/57
    - ALS, 1p. 11/13/57
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/13/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/14/57
  - 1957, December (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - TLS/ALS, 3pp., 12/10/57
    - TLS, 4pp. 12/14/57
  - 1958, January (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - ALS/TLS, 5pp. Sections of novel for McHugh. 1/28/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/28/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/29/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/31/58
  - 1958, February 1-14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/2/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/3/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/4/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/5/58
    - TLS/ALS, 4pp. 2/6/58
    - TLS/ALS, 4pp. 2/7/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/8/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/10/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/10/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/11/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/12/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/14/58
  - 1958, February 15-28 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/15/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/17/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/18/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/19/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/20/58
    - ALS, 6pp. 2/21/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/24/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/24/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/25/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/25/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/27/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/28/58
  - 1958, March 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/2/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/2(?)/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/3/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/4/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/5/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/9/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/10/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/11/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/12/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/13/58
    - ALS/TLS, 4pp. 3/15/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/15/58
  - 1958, March 16-31 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/17/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/18/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/19/58
    - ALS, 4pp. Emily Dickinson. 3/20/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/21/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/23/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/24/58
    - ALS/TLS, 1p. Text from work in progress. 3/24/58
    - TLS/ALS, 3pp. 3/26/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/27/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/29/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 3/31/58
  - 1958, April 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - ALS, 1p. 4/1/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/2/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/3/58
    - ALS, 4pp. James Agee. 4/5/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/8/58
    - ALS, 2pp. Jack Kerouac. 4/9/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/10/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/11/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/12/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/14/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/15/58
  - 1958, April 15-30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/16/58
    - ALS, 1p. 4/17/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/19/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/20/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/21/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/23/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/24/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/25/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/26/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/28/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/29/58
  - 1958, May 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/1/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/1/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/2/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/3/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/5/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/5/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/6/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/7/58
    - ALS, 5pp. Scenes from novel enclosed. 5/8/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/8/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/9/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/11/58
    - ALS, 1p. 5/12/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/13/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/14/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/15/58
  - 1958, May 16-31 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/16/58
    - ALS, 3pp. Marcel Proust 5/18/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/20/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/21/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/23/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/24/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/25/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/27/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/28/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/30/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/31/58
  - 1958, June 1-14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ALS, 2pp. 6/1/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 6/2/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/3/58
    - ALS, 3pp. Kerouac's The Subterraneans and Proust. 6/4/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/5/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/6(?)/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 6/8/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 6/10/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/11/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 6/12/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 6/14/58
  - 1958, June 15-30 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ALS, 7pp. 6/16/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 6/17/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 6/18/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/19/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 6/21/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/23/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 6/26/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 6/28/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/29/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/30/58
  - 1958, July 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/1/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/5/58
    - ALS, 1p. 7/6/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/6/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/7/58
    - ALS, 5pp. Weldon Kees. 7/8/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/9/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/10/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/12/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/13/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/15/58
  - 1958, July 16-31 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - ALS, 4pp. Kenneth Rexroth, Michael Grieg, and Kees 7/16/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/17/58
    - ALS, 3pp. The Death Of A Salesman. 7/19/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 7/20/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/21/58
    - ALS, 1p. 7/22/58
    - ALS, 6pp. 7/23/58
    - ALS, 1p. 7/24/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/25/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/27/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/28/58
    - TLS/ALS, 2pp. 7/29/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/30/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/31/58
  - 1958, August, 1-14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - ALS, 5pp. 8/2/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/5/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 8/6/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/7/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/8/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/10/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/11/58
    - ALS, 4pp. Kerouac's Subterraneans. 8/12/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/13/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/14/58
  - 1958, August 16-31 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/16/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/17/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/18/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/19/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 8/21/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/23/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/24/58
    - ALS, 6pp. 8/25/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/26/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 8/27/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/28/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 8/29/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/31/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/?/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/?/58
  - 1958, September 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - ALS, 6pp. 9/1/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/2/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 9/3/58
    - ALS, 3pp. Jane Austen's Emma. 9/4/58
    - ALS, 3pp. Austen and Wallace Stegner. 9/6/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/7/58
    - ALS, 5pp. Austen's Emma. 9/8/58
    - ALS, 3pp. Austen. 9/9/58
    - ALS, 11pp. 9/10/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/11/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/13/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/14/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/15/58
  - 1958, September 16-30 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - ALS, 3pp. Dr. Zhivago. 9/16/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/17/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/18/58
    - ALS, 7pp. 9/20/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/21/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 9/22/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/23/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/24/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/25/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 9/26/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/28/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/29/58
    - ALS, 1p. 9/30/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 9/30/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/?/58
  - 1958, October 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 5pp. Proust. 10/1/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/2/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/3/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/5/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/6/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 10/7/58
    - ALS, 3pp. Rexroth. 10/8/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/9/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/10/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/12/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/13/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/14/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 10/15/58
  - 1958, October 16-31 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - ALS, 1p. 10/16/58
    - ALS, 7pp. 10/17/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 10/19/58
    - ALS, 5pp. Kerouac's The Dharma Bums. 10/20/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/21/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/22/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/23/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/24/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/27/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/28/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/29/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 10/30/58
  - 1958, November 1-15 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/1/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/2/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/3/58
    - ALS, 3pp. Saint John Perse. 11/4/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/6/58
    - ALS, 4pp. Pasternak. 11/6/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/8/58
    - ALS, 4pp. Joseph Wechsberg. 11/9/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/11/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/15/58
    - ALS, 1p. 11/15/58
    - ALS, 8pp. 11/15/58
  - 1958, November 16-30 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/17/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/18/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/19/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/20/58
    - ALS, 7pp. 11/21/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/23/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/24/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 11/25/58
    - ALS, 9pp. 11/26/58
    - ALS, 8pp. 11/27/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/28/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 11/29/58
    - ALS, 6pp. 11/30/58
  - 1958, December 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/1/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/2/58
    - ALS, 3pp. Perse. 12/3/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 12/4/58
    - ALS, 9pp. 12/6/58
    - ALS, 16pp. 12/7/58
    - ALS, 7pp. 12/9/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/10/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 12/11/58
    - ALS, 7pp. 12/12/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 12/14/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/15/58
  - 1958, December 16-31 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/16/58
    - Christmas Card. 12/16/58
    - ALS, 1p. 12/17/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/18/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 12/19/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 12/20/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 12/22/58
    - ALS, 4pp. Charlie "Bird" Parker. 12/24/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/26/58
    - ALS, 7pp. 12/31/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 12(?)/?/58(?)
  - 1959, January 1-14 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/1/59
    - ALS, 5pp. Rexroth. 1/3/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/4/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/5/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/6/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Perse. 1/7/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/8/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/10/59
    - ALS/TLS, 2pp. One page section from novel. 1/10/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/11/59
    - ALS/TLS, 4pp. One page section from novel. 1/12/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/13/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/14/59
  - 1959, January 15-31 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/17/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/17/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/18/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/19/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Jean Cocteau. Thomas the Impostor. 1/21/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/21/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/21/59
    - ALS, 1p. 1/22/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Basil Bunting. 1/22/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/24/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/26/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/27/59
    - ALS, 1p. 1/28/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/29/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/31/59
  - 1959, February, 1-14 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/2/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/3/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Crevecoeur and Van Wyck Brooks. 2/4/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/5/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/7/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Crevecoeur. 2/8/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Crevecoeur. 2/9/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/10/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Tillie Olsen and Jessamyn West. 2/10/59
    - ALS, 1p. 2/11/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Crevecoeur and Rilke. 2/11/59
  - 1959, February 15-28 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/15/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/17/59
    - ALS, 2pp. Rexroth. 2/18/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/20/59
    - ALS, 7pp. The Seventh Seal. Wallace Stegner. 2/22/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/22/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Jean Jacques Rousseau's Confessions. 2/24/59
    - ALS/TLS, 6pp. A section of the novel enclosed. 2/24/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/25/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/26/59
    - ALS, 2pp. John Millington Synge's Playboy of the Western World. 2/27/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/28/59
  - 1959, March 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/2/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/3/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/4/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/7/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/7/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/8/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/9/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Proust. 3/10/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/11/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/13/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/14/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/15/59
  - 1959, March 16-31 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - ALS, 4pp. Film Richard III. Proust. 3/16/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/18/59
    - ALS, 1p. 3/18/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/19/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/21/59
    - ALS, 2pp. Proust. 3/22/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/23/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Henry James' Sacred Fount. 3/24/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/26/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/26/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/27/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/28/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/29/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/30/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/31/59
  - 1959, April 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - ALS, 4pp. Proust. 4/1/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/2/59
    - ALS, 1p. 4/4/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/5/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/5/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Evelyn Waugh. 4/7/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/9/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/10/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/11/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Dorothy Van Ghent. 4/13/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/14/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/15/59
  - 1959, April 16-30 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/16/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/17/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/18/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/20/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/21/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/22/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/23/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/24/59
    - ALS, 4pp. ee cummings. Fidel Castro. 4/26/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 4/27/59
    - ALS, 2pp. Ford Madox Ford's The Good Soldier. 4/28/59
    - ALS, 2pp. The Good Soldier. 4/29/59
  - 1959, May 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 3pp. Castro. 5/2/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Allen Ginsberg. 5/2/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Castro. 5/3/59
    - ALS, 2pp. Kerouac and Proust. 5/4/59
    - ALS, 2pp. Ginsberg. 5/5/59
    - ALS, 5pp. Film Some Like It Hot. C. H. Kwock 5/7/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Ginsberg. 5/9/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/10/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/11/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/12/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/13/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/14/59
  - 1959, May 16-31 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - ALS, 5pp. Dennis Murphy's The Sergeant. 5/16/59
    - ALS, 1p. 5/17/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/18/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/18/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/19/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 5/20/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 5/21/59
    - ALS, 6pp. Joseph Conrad's The Shadow Line. 5/25/59
  - ALS, 4pp. 5/27/59 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/28/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Sydney Freedberg. 5/29/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Proust. Conrad. 5/30/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/31/59
  - 1959, June (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/1/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 6/2/59
    - ALS, 5pp. John F. Kennedy. 6/3/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/4/59
    - ALS, 8pp. Stegner. J. D. Salinger. 6/7/59
    - ALS, 4pp. Van Wyck Brooks. 6/9/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 6/10/59
    - ALS, 1p. 6/11/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 6/16/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/17/59
  - Obscured Postmarks (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - ALS, 3pp. Friday. ?/?/57
    - ALS, 3pp. Wednesday. ?/?/57
    - ALS, 4pp. Saturday. ?/?/57
    - ALS, 4pp. Tuesday. ?/?/?
    - ALS, 3pp. Monday morning. Crevecouer. ?/?/59(?)
    - ALS, 4pp. Tuesday. ?/?/59
    - ALS, 3pp. Thursday. ?/?/?
    - ALS, 5pp. Friday. ?/?/?
- Addendum
  - 1957, August (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - ALS, 3pp. (South Natick) 8/20?/57
  - 1957, September (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - TLS/ALS, 2pp. 11/15/57
    - TLS/ALS, 2pp. 11/16/57
    - TLS/ALS, 8pp. 11/18/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/18/57
    - TLS, 1p. 11/19/57
    - TLS, 2pp. 11/21/57
    - TLS, 3pp. 11/21/57
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/23/57
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/26/57
    - ALS, 4+pp. 11/26/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/28/57
    - ALS, 5pp. 11/30/57
  - 1957, December (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/1/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 12/2/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/4/57
    - ALS, 4pp. (TS + holograph) 12/5/57
    - ALS, 5pp. 12/7/57
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/8/57
    - ALS, 4pp. (TS + holograph)- Monday 12/10/57
    - ALS, 2pp. (Tuesday night) 12/12/57
    - ALS, Christmas Card 12/13/57
    - ALS, 4pp. (Thursday) 12/14/57
    - ALS, 2pp. (Monday) 12/18/57
  - 1957, December (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - ALS, 2+pp. 12/20/57
    - ALS, 2pp. 12/22/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/22/57
    - ALS, 1p. 12/23/57
    - ALS, 3p. 12/26/57
    - TLS, 1+pp. 12/28/57
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/28/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/29/57
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/30/57
  - 1958, January, ALS, 3pp. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    1/2/58
    - ALS, 3+pp. 1/3/58
    - ALS, 8pp. 1/5/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/6/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/8/58
    - ALS, 4pp. (Pencil) 1/8/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/9/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/10/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/14/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/14/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/15/58
    - ALS, 1p. 1/17/58
  - 1958, January (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - ALS, 2+pp. 1/17/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/19/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/20/58
    - ALS, 2+pp. 1/21/58
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/22/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/23/58
    - ALS, 1p. 1/24/58
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/25/58
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/26/58
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/28/58
  - 1958, October (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - ALS, 2pp. (Peterborough, NH) 10/15/58
  - 1958, November (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - ALS, 3pp. (Peterborough, NH) 11/7/58
  - 1958, December (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - ALS, 2pp. (Glendale, OH) 12/29/58
    - ALS, 6pp. (Glendale, OH) 12/29/58
  - 1959, June (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 5pp. 6/12/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 6/14/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 6/15/59
    - ALS, 5+pp. (Wed) 6/18/59
    - ALS, 6pp. (Thurs night) 6/19/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 6/21/59
    - ALS, 1p. 6/22/59
    - ALS, 4pp. (Monday) 6/22/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/24/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 6/27/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 6/28/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/28/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 6/30/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 6/30/59
  - 1959, July (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/1/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/2/59
    - ALS, 5pp. (Thurs & Fri) 7/3/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/4/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/6/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/7/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/9/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/9/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/11/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/12/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/13/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/14/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/14/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/15/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/17/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/19/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/20/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/21/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/22/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/23/59
    - ALS, 3pp. (Sat) 7/25/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 7/27/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 7/28/59
    - ALS, 3+pp. 7/29/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 7/30/59
  - 1959, August (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/1/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/3/59
    - ALS, 1p. 8/3/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 8/4/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 8/5/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 8/6/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/8/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/9/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/10/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 8/11/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/12/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 8/13/59
    - ALS, 1p. 8/15/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/15/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/17/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/18/59
    - ALS, 8pp. 8/19/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 8/20/59
    - ALS, 3+pp. 8/22/59
    - ALS, 6pp. 8/23/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/24/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 8/25/59
    - ALS, 7pp. (Cambridge) 8/26/59
    - ALS, 6pp. 8/27/59
    - ALS, 4+pp. (Fri night) 8/29/59
    - ALS, 9pp. (Sat night) 8/30/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 8/31/59
  - 1959, September 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - ALS, 5pp. 9/2/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/3/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/5/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/7/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/7/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/8/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 9/9/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/10/59
  - 1959, September 13-30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/13/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/14/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/16/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/17/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/18/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/19/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/21/59
    - ALS, 4pp. (Monday night) 9/22/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 9/23/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 9/24/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/26/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 9/28/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/29/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 9/30/59
  - 1959, October 1-16 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/1/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/2/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/5/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/7/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/9/59
    - ALS, 1p. 10/10/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/10/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/12/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/14/59
    - ALS, 1p. 10/15/59
    - ALS, 6pp. 10/16/59
  - 1959, October 17-31 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/17/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/19/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/20/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/21/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/22/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/24/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 10/25/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/26/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 10/27/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 10/28/59
    - ALS, 3pp. (Pencil) 10/29/59
    - ALS, 2+pp. 10/31/59
  - 1959, November 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - ALS, 3+pp. 11/2/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/3/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/4/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 11/5/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 11/6/59
    - ALS, 5pp. 11/9/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/10/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/11/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/12/59
  - 1959, November 16-30 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - ALS, 4pp. 11/16/59
    - ALS, 6pp. 11/17/59
    - ALS, 9pp. 11/17/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/20/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/21/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/23/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/24/59
    - ALS, 1p. 11/24/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/25/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 11/25/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/28/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 11/30/59
  - 1959, December (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/4/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/7/59
    - ALS, 2+pp. (pencil) 12/18/59
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil) 12/21/59
    - ALS, 4pp. 12/22/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/23/59
    - ALS, 3pp. 12/24/59
    - ALS, 2pp. 12/28/59
    - ALS, 4pp. (Glendale, OH) 12/29/59
  - 1960, January 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - ALS, 3pp. (red ink + pencil) 1/4/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/5/60
    - ALS, postcard (pencil) 1/5/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/6/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/7/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/8/60
    - ALS, 3+pp. 1/9/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/11/60
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/12/60
    - ALS, 4+pp. 1/13/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/14/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 1/15/60
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/16/60
  - 1960, January 16-30 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/16/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/18/60
    - ALS, 1p. 1/19/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/21/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 1/22/60
    - ALS, 6pp. 1/24/60
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/25/60
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/27/60
    - ALS, 5pp. 1/28/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 1/30/60
  - 1960, February (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/1/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/2/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/3/60
    - ALS, 2pp. + TS 1p. 2/3/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/4/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 2/6/60
    - ALS, 2+pp. 2/9/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/10/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/12/60
    - ALS, 2+pp. 2/13/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/15/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/17/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 2/19/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/20/60
    - ALS, 1+pp. 2/23/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 2/24/60
    - ALS, 1p. 2/27/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil) 2/28/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (ink & pencil) 2/29/60
  - 1960, March (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/2/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/5/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/7/60
    - ALS, 5pp. 3/7/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/8/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/9/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/11/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/14/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 3/15/60
    - ALS, 4pp. (pencil) 3/16/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 3/18/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/19/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/21/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/23/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/24/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil) 3/26/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 3/28/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil) 3/29/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 3/30/60
  - 1960, April (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/1/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/2/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 4/5/60
    - ALS, 8pp. (note paper, ring binder) 4/6/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/8/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/9/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/11/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/12/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/13/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 4/15/60
    - ALS, 7pp. (pencil + ink) 4/17/60
    - ALS, 4pp. (pencil + ink) 4/19/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil + ink) 4/20/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 4/23/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil + ink) 4/25/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/25/60
    - ALS, 1p. 4/27/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 4/29/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 4/29/60
  - 1960, May (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - ALS, 4+pp. 5/2/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/2/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/4/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 5/4/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/7/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/9/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil) 5/11/60
    - ALS, 3+pp. (pencil) 5/12/60
    - ALS, 3+pp. (pencil) 5/13/60
    - ALS, 4pp. 5/17/60
    - ALS, 2+pp. 5/18/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/18/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 5/19/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 5/21/60
    - ALS, 3pp. (pencil) (Yaddo) 5/23/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/25/60
    - ALS, 2pp. 5/26/60
    - ALS, 3pp. 5/28/60
  - 1960, June (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 6/1/60
    - ALS, 4pp. (pencil) 6/1/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 6/2/60
    - ALS, 2pp. (pencil) 6/4/60